这里只有一只
There's only one here.
它们是锻造成一对的
They were forged as a pair.
继续找 一定埋在别的地方
We'll keep looking for it. It must be buried elsewhere.
别的地方?
Elsewhere?
哪里
Like where?
(欢迎来到泽西市)
卡玛拉 你在写作业吗
Kamala! Are you doing your homework, beta?
对 科学作业
Yeah! Science!
砰
Boom!
卡玛拉·克汗登场
Enter, Kamala Khan.
准备
Ready for...
惊奇队长
Captain Marvel.
她需要我帮忙
She needs my help.
看我大展身手
Shine on, baby.
手怎么这么难画啦
Why are hands so hard to draw?
惊奇少女及时抵达
Okay, Ms. Marvel arrives, and just in time...
复仇者联盟也需要支援
...'cause even the Avengers need backup, ya know?
轰 卡啪
Wham! Kapow!
我的机会来了
This is my chance!
啪
Pow!
砰
Boom!
不错嘛 小鬼
Not bad, kid.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
惊奇少女
Ms. Marvel.
妹子
Dude.
同名姐妹
Twinsies!
(同名姐妹)
想参加复仇者联盟的派对吗
Hey, you wanna go party with the Avengers?
想啊
Uh... Yeah!
你会飞吗
Can you fly?
不会 但我会这招
No, but I can do this!
卡玛拉 别逼我上去哦
Kamala! Don't make me come up there!
-听起来不像科学作业 -好啦
-That does not sound like science to me. -Okay.
(当天稍早)
你什么都不记得吗
You don't remember anything?
我看到...
I see...
一些片段
flashes.
短暂的时刻
Little moments.
如果我能拼凑那天早上的记忆
If I could just piece together what happened that morning...
或许就能厘清真相
maybe it'll all make sense.
你们从我家 我家人朋友手中抢走我
You stole me from my home, my family, my friends.
小麻烦中尉
Lieutenant Trouble.
-更高 更远 更快 -没错
-Higher, further, faster, baby. -That's right.
告诉至高智慧我会让它划下终点
Tell the Supreme Intelligence that I'm coming to end it.
战争 谎言
The war, the lies.
全部
All of it.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
我一转眼就回来了
I'll be back before you know it.
我能飞上天 在半途中见你
I could fly up and meet you halfway.
等你学会跟卡萝阿姨一样发光
Only if you learn to glow like your Auntie Carol.
(路易斯安那州居民飞上天际)
过来 呆头鹅
Come here, Goosey.
尼克·福瑞来电
Incoming call from Nick Fury.
你在等电话吗
You expecting a call?
我们转到语音信箱好了
Maybe we just send it to voice mail.
尼克·福瑞
Nick Fury...
我最喜欢的独眼特务
my favorite one-eyed man of intrigue.
卡萝·丹佛斯
Carol Danvers.
银河浪女
Prodigal child of the Milky Way.
那边情况如何
How goes it out there?
好得很
Thriving.
什么东西
What the hell was that?
-呆头鹅吗  -对
-Goose? -Yeah.
你呢
What about you?
你好吗
How are you doing?
你知道几小时前跳跃点系统有突波吗
What do you know about the surge in the jump point system a few hours ago?
我没注意到异常现象
I didn't notice anything unusual.
我来看看
I'll take a look now.
干扰到整个系统
It rattled the whole system.
我们正在了解来龙去脉
We're trying to get a handle on what happened.
整个网络都受影响
The entire network was affected?
对 从头到尾
Yeah. End to end.
幸好我们的神经网络团队
Thankfully, our neural network team...
追踪源头到MB-418
was able to trace the origin back to MB-418.
-你在那附近吧 -对
-You're in the neighborhood, right? -Yeah.
你能查查看吗
Can you check it out?
-马上办 -感谢
-I'm on it. -Appreciate you.
莫妮卡的团队收到情报就会立刻传达
Monica and her team will send more intel as they acquire it.
莫妮卡
Monica?
她在那边干嘛 我以为她在地球
What's she doing there? I thought that she was on Earth.
-她还好吗 -还好
-Is she okay? -Yeah.
她不是你印象中的小女生了
And she's not that little kid you remember.
我们能在晚餐前完成吗
So, do we think that we can finish this before dinner?
我们应该来不及修好
Yeah. I don't think we're gonna fix it in time
取得跳跃点的读数
to get a reading on the jump point.
我知道某人的超能力有办法
But I do know someone with superpowers who could.
噢
Oh.
好 我去
Fine. I'll go.
你们进去看看网络的状态
You guys head in and check the status of the network.
查出受损情形才能修复
We've gotta find this damage and see if we can reverse it.
是 上尉
Aye, aye, Captain.
福瑞
Fury...
我查到了
I think I found something.
通讯改为手控
Communications override.
蓝博上尉 太空船外
Captain Rambeau. Spacewalk.
已连线
Connected.
蓝博
Rambeau...
你在干什么
what the hell are you doin'?
突波似乎在跳跃点留下残余效应
Seems the surge has had some residual effect on the jump point.
我传读数给你 福瑞
I'm gonna get you some readings, Fury.
莫...
Mon...
-喂  -莫妮卡
-Hello? -Monica.
喂
Hello?
那是莫妮卡吗
Was that Monica?
-卡萝阿姨 -福瑞
-Aunt Carol? -Fury...
-那是莫妮卡吗 -想跟她讲话吗
-was that Monica? -Why, you wanna talk to her?
我现在的状况
I don't think I'm in the best...
不太适合 我不...
position to... I... I don't...
我不想...
I don't wanna...
听着...
Look...
我不想这样跟她讲话
I don't wanna talk to her like this.
-都过了这么久 -其实...
-Not after all this time. -You know...
-你终究得和她说话 -我知道
-eventually you're gonna have to talk to her. -I know.
我知道 可是...
I know, but...
等我回到里面再跟家人团聚
let's save the family reunions till I'm back inside.
我发现突波的来源了
I think I found the source of the surge.
你看到什么
What are you seeing?
它是个跳跃点 但没有关闭 好像...
It's a jump point, but it's not closing. Like...
卡住了
it's stuck.
丹佛斯
Danvers.
Danvers!
跳跃点仍在渗漏能量
The jump point's still leaking energy.
-上尉 喂 -喂
-Captain Rambeau? -Hello?
-喂 -莫妮卡
-Hello? -Monica.
好美
Beautiful.
我的天啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
别转了 拜托
Stop spinning, stop spinning, stop spinning, please!
是尼克·福瑞 嗨
It's Nick Fury! Hey!
你怎么...
How did you... Oh, wow.
我是卡玛拉·克汗 不 我是惊奇少女
I'm Kamala Khan. No, sorry, I'm Ms. Marvel, actually.
来自泽西市
But I'm from Jersey City and I...
糟糕 我没戴招牌面罩
Oh, no, I don't have my mask on.
这是复仇者联盟测验吗
Is this an Avengers test?
你究竟是谁
Who the hell are you?
(惊奇队长  赞)
(永远的好朋友)
嗨
Hi.
好漂亮的客厅
Really good living room.
-卡玛拉 -卡玛拉
-Kamala? -Kamala?
你们对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
-达本想干嘛 -太迟了
-What is Dar-Benn doing? -It's too late.
至高者已经在塔奈星上了
The Supremor's already on Tarnax.
你阻止不了
You can't stop this.
等着瞧
Watch me.
福瑞 是克里人
Fury. It's the Kree.
他们要攻击塔奈星上的史克鲁尔人
They're going after the Skrulls on Tarnax.
等一下 别冲动
Now, hold on. Do not go in swinging.
-这是一趟和平与和解之旅 -福瑞
-This is a peace and reconciliation tour. -Fury.
-我来处理 -卡萝...
-I got this. -Carol...
我跟叫卡玛拉·克汗的人交换位置
So, I switched with someone named Kamala Khan?
对 她好像跟你一样糊涂
Yeah. She seemed to be as confused as you are.
她的超能力不包含瞬间移动
Well, there's nothing in her power-set about teleportation.
别再聊她了
Enough about her.
我想知道你在MB-418上的遭遇
I wanna know what happened to you on MB-418.
是
Yes, sir.
我得先说我不太确定 不过...
Let me preface this by saying I'm not really sure. But...
我没弄坏衣柜门 我在太空上
I did not break my closet door, okay? I was in space.
-它自己坏的 -不是 我消失了
-Oh, so it broke itself? -No, no, no. See, I disappeared.
说不定是惊奇队长弄坏的
So maybe Captain Marvel broke it.
-什么 -对 你朋友惊奇队长
-What? -Yes, your friend, Captain Marvel.
她在我们客厅走来走去
She was walking up and down our living room...
现在你回家
and now you come back...
飘进来却没道歉
waltzing in with no apologies.
惊奇队长来我们家?
I'm sorry, Captain Marvel was in our house?
惊奇队长有对你施压吗
Is Captain Marvel pressuring you in any way?
我明白她是个大人物
Look, I understand that she's an important figure and all that...
但你不必对她言听计从
but you don't have to do as she says.
不 她们根本是一起合作
No, no, they're clearly working together.
-看她笑成那样 -闭嘴
-Look at her face. Look at her smile. -Aamir, stop it.
-她又在搞神秘 -别找你妹的碴
-She's being super secretive as always. -Aamir, stop picking on your sister.
-看看她 -穆妮芭
-Look at her. -Muneeba.
卡玛拉 你又在说谎了吗
Kamala, are you lying again?
-跟我说你是否 -我女儿没说谎
-Just tell me if you're involved or... -My daughter has said she's not lying.
-卡玛拉 -她明明...
-Kamala. -Looks like she's having...
-很开心 -穆妮芭
-so much fun. -Muneeba...
-她不会保密 -天啊 是真的
-She's bad at keeping secrets. -Oh, my God! It's happening!
接近塔奈星
Approaching Tarnax.
警告
Warning.
侦测到克里人船舰
Kree ship detected.
(塔奈星 史克鲁尔难民移居地)
这不是我们说好的 达本
This is not what we agreed, Dar-Benn.
至高者达本
Supremor Dar-Benn.
史克鲁尔人
The Skrull...
已经散落在宇宙各角落
have been scattered to every corner of the universe.
到哪里都成为难民 不过...
Made refugees wherever we go, and still...
我们还是抱持诚恳态度进行谈判
we came into these negotiations in good faith.
我了解 卓治
I hear you, Dro'ge.
我或许比任何人更了解你们吃的苦
I, perhaps more than anyone, understand what you and your people have been through.
在我的前任垮台后
After my predecessor was destroyed...
异端分子填补空缺
heretics rose up to fill the void.
内战污染了天空 我们族人无法呼吸
The Civil War has polluted our skies. My people cannot breathe.
我们的太阳奄奄一息
Our sun is dying.
哈拉星时序紊乱
Hala is out of time.
我希望我们能一起重建
I hope we can rebuild together.
我甚至愿意放下祖先的仇恨
So much so that I'm willing to put our ancient animosities behind us.
给你们机会保护族人
And give you a chance to protect your people.
不再逃亡
To stop running.
史克鲁尔人将在克里帝国占一席之地
The Skrull will take their rightful place in the Kree Empire.
我将协助他们迁移
And I will aid in their relocation.
-迁移 -什么意思
-Relocation? -What?
我可不愿剥夺大气层 让你们受苦
I would hate for your people to suffocate when I strip the atmosphere.
是歼灭者
It's the Annihilator!
天啊
Oh, my God!
-怎么回事 -对啊 怎么回事
-What the hell is going on? -Yes, what the hell is going on?
我在一艘太空船上 然后就瞬移过来
I was on some freaky spaceship and then I teleported here.
不知是不是我的新能力
I don't know if that's my new power.
-这只怪猫吃了一个人 -猫会吃人
-And then this freaking cat ate a man. -How can a cat eat a man, Kamala?
不知道 它有触手
I don't know. It has tentacles...
-吃了一个人 -什么触手
-and it ate a man. -What tentacles, Kamala?
-不知道 -触手在哪
-I don't know. -Where are the tentacles?
从它嘴巴冒出来
It comes out of his mouth, and they're...
-天啊 -噢
-Oh, my God! -Oh!
天啊 又来了
Oh, my God, it's happening again!
-不 -卡玛拉 他们是谁
-Oh, no, no, no. -Kamala, who are they?
快跑
Please run.
你怎么来的 又怎么扯进来
How did you get here, and how're you involved in this?
克里人在MB-418弄了个虫洞
The Kree jury-rigged a wormhole on MB-418.
像跳跃点
You mean like a jump point?
-不知道 我碰了一下 -为什么
-I don't know. But I touched it and then I... -Why'd you do that?
它在发光又很神秘
Because it was glowing and mysterious.
新规定 不准乱碰
Okay, new rule, no more touching shit.
尤其是发光的神秘物体
Especially glowing, mysterious shit.
我感受到你满满的负能量
Okay, I'm feeling a lot of negative energy from you...
我不喜欢 那不是重点
and I don't like it. That's not the point. The point is...
重点是它抽走大气 还这样
is that it was siphoning off the atmosphere. And it did this!
剪刀赢布
Scissors beat paper.
福瑞 有能量绕着我的手转 专心
Fury! There was, like, energy that went around my hand. Focus.
好 不然我这样
Okay, maybe if I do this.
歼灭者
Annihilator.
我不喜欢这名字
I don't like that name.
-你朋友 -你好
-Friends of yours? -Hi.
歼灭者
Annihilator!
阿米尔 压住他
Aamir, get him!
压住他
Get him! Hit him!
优素福
Yusuf!
放开我
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
卡玛拉 你还好吗
Kamala, are you okay?
福瑞
Fury!
我只要传递辐射 就会瞬间移动
I think I'm getting teleported whenever I channel any kind of radiant...
我使用超能力就会转换位置
I think I switch when I use my powers.
很有可能
Strong theory.
我们的测试不断产生相同结果
Our tests keep generating the same result.
只要有新的跳跃点 这手环就更不稳
With each new jump point, this band becomes more unstable.
我强烈建议等待第二只手环
I strongly suggest we wait for the second band.
又见面了
Hi, again.
之前的事很抱歉
So sorry about earlier.
我们找卡玛拉·克汗
We're looking for Kamala Khan.
我入选了吗
Did I get in?
新苹果平板 没看过
Is this the new iPad? I haven't seen it yet.
他们哪比得上
They wish!
-走了 -就是啊
-All right. Come on, let's go. -I know. Wait...
最高机密情报怎么是透明的
if this is all top secret information, why is it on a clear case?
因为...
Well...
滑一下就好 嗨
just... swipe it a little bit... Hi.
相信吗 他们有我的资料
Can you believe it? They have intel on me.
是我耶
On me!
我的资料耶
I am intel.
瞧瞧你
Look at you!
神刃代表什么
Hey, what does S.A.B.E.R. stand for?
策略航太生物物理
Strategic Aerospace Biophysics...
-与外星语言回应 -这是机密
-and Exolinguistic Response. -That's classified.
抱歉
Sorry.
"硬光超能力" 有
"Hard Light powers," yes.
-诺尔 -你们为何有她的资料
-"Noor..." -Okay, but why do you have intel on her?
有人在监视我们吗
Is there some sort of surveillance on us?
-说监视太严重了 -女士
-"Surveillance" is a strong word. -Well, ma'am...
你女儿是拯救泽西市的英雄
your daughter is the hero that saved Jersey City.
我们当然有她的资料
So, of course we would have intel on someone like her. And you're also...
-你也经过电磁异变 -什么意思
-electromagnetically altered. -What does that mean?
意思是我们俩都有
Oh, it just means that we both have...
光基超能力
light-based powers.
你的代号是什么
What's your code name?
我没有代号
Oh, I don't have a code name.
-我们再讨论 -不了 谢谢
-We'll workshop it. -No, thank you.
卡萝阿姨
Aunt Carol...
惊奇队长也有光基超能力
Captain Marvel also has light-based powers.
应该不是巧合
It's probably not a coincidence.
更别提你们俩直接碰到
Not to mention the two of you came into direct contact...
一些失灵的跳跃点
with some malfunctioning jump points.
不敢相信惊奇队长来过 我却没见到
I still cannot believe that Captain Marvel was here and I didn't even get to meet her.
我们是同名姐妹哦
You know, we're supposed to be all, like "twinsies!" you know.
名字相同 我一定会...
We have the same name. I would obviously, then...
我会把我写的信交给她
I don't know, I would just give her the letter I wrote for her...
跟她出去吃饭 然后...
and we would go out for lunch, and then it would just...
你说"卡萝阿姨"
Did you say "Aunt Carol?"
我说惊奇队长
I said that Captain Marvel...
能吸收光能
can absorb light energy.
我看得见
I can see it.
你能把光
And you, you can turn light...
变成实体
into physical matter.
这我没听过
Which I have never heard of.
-我的假设 -我能秀给你看
-But my working theory... -I could totally show you.
不要
No!
搞什...
What the...
嗨
Hi.
她们不像亲戚
Nah, they don't seem related.
随便 家家有本难念的经
Whatever, Yusuf. Families are complicated.
莫妮卡 要跟卡萝说说你的推论吗
Monica, you wanna fill Carol in on your working theory?
好
Yeah.
你好 惊奇队长
Hi, Captain Marvel.
很高兴见到你 小麻烦中尉
It is so good to see you, Lieutenant Trouble.
我也是
You too.
现在是蓝博上尉了
And it's Captain Rambeau now.
对 抱歉
Right. Sorry.
有什么新消息
So, what's new?
我妹妹在哪
Where's my sister?
我想我们都接触到那些不稳的跳跃点
I'm thinking that our joint exposure to these unsteady jump points...
也容易受电磁能影响
and our susceptibility to electromagnetic energy...
让我们的世界线短暂缠结
has temporarily entangled our world-lines.
就是那样
Yeah, that, right there.
缠结 我们的光能力缠结在一起
Entanglement. Our light powers are entangled.
同时使用它们 我们就会交换位置
So, we switch places whenever we use them at the same time.
-所以卡玛拉... -你何时获得超能力
-Which would mean Kamala... -When did you get powers?
我走过女巫咒圈的辐射屏蔽障碍
I walked through a radiation shielding barrier...
现在能操控并看见
of a witch hex and now I can manipulate and see...
电磁频谱上的所有波长
all wavelengths of the electromagnetic spectrum.
真替你开心
I'm very happy for you. Yeah.
-我们女儿呢 -拜托 卡玛拉呢
-Where's our daughter? -Yes, please. Where is Kamala?
在你原本的位置
Wherever you were.
-你刚刚在哪 -谁是卡玛拉
-Where were you? -Who's Kamala?
跟我们交换位置的第三人
The third person we're switching with.
-光能力少女 你在哪 -你干嘛
-Light powers. Teenage girl. Where were you? -What are you doing?
-你在干嘛 -我想交换位置
-What are you doing? -I'm trying to switch.
竟然没用
Why isn't it working when I need it to work?
丹佛斯
Danvers, Danvers!
-好乱 -跟卡玛拉说她老爸很不爽
-So confused. -Tell Kamala that her Abu is very upset.
要去哪 去干嘛
Where are we going and why are we going there?
-卡萝 -卡萝 你要去哪
-Carol! -Carol, where you going?
天啊
Oh, my God!
莫妮卡 你得飞上去
Monica, you gotta fly.
不 我
No, no, no. I...
我知道
I mean, I know.
严格说来我还没飞过
But technically, I haven't done that yet!
现在非飞不可
Yeah, well, you got to now...
否则卡玛拉高中毕不了业
or Kamala's not gonna graduate from high school.
快点 用你的核心肌群
Come on! Use your core!
天啊
Oh, jeez.
黑人女力
Hey. Black Girl Magic.
我来了
I got you! I got you!
我抓住你
I got you!
惨了
Oops!
等一下
Hold on!
发生什么事
What is happening?
我飞行时抓不住你
I can't hold on to you while I'm flying.
天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-我们死定了 -抓紧
-We're gonna die! -Hold on!
抓紧 我在想办法
Hold on! I'm thinking, I'm thinking!
等等 我想到了
Wait, I have an idea.
抱住我
Grab on to me!
这样最好有用
This had better work!
没事 是卡萝
Oh, it's cool. It's Carol.
别发功
Okay, no powers, no powers. Just...
她们是谁
Who are they?
她们是惊奇队长的同伙
They are associates of Captain Marvel.
歼灭者来了
The Annihilator is here?
来过 然后这两个就出现了
Yeah, well, she was. And then these two just sort of appeared.
那只手环呢
What about the band?
如果她干预 我现在就得出手
If she's meddling, I need to strike now.
我还是不懂MB-418为何不稳
Yeah. I still can't account for the instabilities exhibited on MB-418.
-这玩意的威力不只... -可是有用
-This thing does much more than just... -But it works?
对 如果给我更多时间
Yes. Yes. But if you give me more time...
-我能让它更安全 -不行
-I can make it safer. -No.
现在就开始
No. We do it now.
趁歼灭者尚未出现
Before the Annihilator appears.
这两个该怎么处置
What should we do about... these two?
你
You.
等一下
Hold that thought.
我们得抢走她的手环
We gotta get that band off of her.
它跟我的好像
It looks like mine.
姐姐
Guys!
我不会飞
I can't fly.
有太空船能借我吗
Do you guys have a spaceship I could borrow or...
卡玛拉 别跟他们说话
Kamala, don't talk to them.
你知道我的名字
You know my name!
克里人来此 希望
The Kree came here hopeful...
-我们能签和平协议 -你做了什么
-that we could build a covenant of peace. -What have you done?
结果你们派歼灭者攻击我们
But then you sic the Annihilator on us.
把我们当成害虫
Like we're vermin.
史克鲁尔人再次背叛克里人
Once again, the Skrull have betrayed the Kree.
因此...
And for that...
卡萝 我们得带这些人离开
Carol, we gotta get these people out of here.
卓治皇帝
Emperor Dro'ge...
你必须立刻撤离族人
you need to evacuate your people now.
我们无处可去
We have nowhere to go.
卡萝 那些船...
Carol, the ships...
他们逃不掉的
they're not gonna make it.
回船上 别使用超能力
Get back to the ship and don't use your powers.
-我能帮忙 -快去
-But I can help. -Now.
-快走 -卡玛拉呢
-Let's go. -Where's Kamala?
卡玛拉
Kamala!
不
No!
快走
Let's go, let's go!
-快点 -快进去
-Come on! -Keep moving...
拜托
please, please.
-这些人... -快走
-All these people, they're gonna... -Come on, sweetie.
-不 怎能丢下他们 -卡玛拉快走
-No! How can you just leave them here? -Kamala, now!
我们得救能救的人
We need to save who we can.
讯号已送出
Transmission sent.
嘿
Hey.
这项和平协议
This peace treaty...
是好事
it was a good thing.
-它是诡计 -如果是...
-It was a ruse. -If it were...
你出手干预也失败了
your intervention failed.
我们不需要你帮忙了
We don't need your help anymore.
我联络上一个朋友
I called a friend.
她能为你们找到栖身之所
She can find a safe place for you.
可以吗
Is that okay?
我们别无选择
We have no choice.
来了
Incoming.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
再次谢谢你
Thank you again.
别客气
Always.
你终于组成了一个团队
I see that you've finally found yourself a team.
无心插柳
It is unintentional.
我自己也加入一个无心插柳团队
Oh, I've been on some unintentional teams myself.
-我知道 -你不必孤军奋战了
-I know, but... -You can stand tall without standing alone.
相信我 惊奇队长
Take it from me, Marv.
嗨
Hey.
惊奇队长会解决的
Captain Marvel will fix this.
我保证
I promise.
谢谢
Thank you.
愿下次欢喜相见
May our next meeting be joyful.
(哈拉星)
可以呼吸了
Breathe.
你们记得吗
Do you remember?
太阳曾经照耀着哈拉星
When the sun used to shine on Hala?
我们的家园有多么美丽
How beautiful our home was?
在她来临之前
Before her?
在歼灭者来临之前
Before the Annihilator.
我在场
I was there.
我听见她的谎言
I heard her lies...
宣称她是来解救我们的
claiming she was there to set us free.
可是当她摧毁至高智慧
But when she destroyed the Supreme Intelligence...
也消灭了克里人
she destroyed the Kree.
30年来我与各位并肩作战
For 30 years I have been fighting alongside you.
我不但带来和平
Not only have I brought you peace...
也设法让哈拉星重返荣耀
but I have found a way to return Hala to glory.
至高者
Supremor!
重燃太阳需要比那手环更强的力量
We need more power than that band can provide if we're to reignite our sun.
那么多能量
That amount of energy...
会杀死你
Well, it would kill you.
如果代价是我的性命 我愿意
If my life is the cost, so be it.
我们会及时找到另一只
We will find the other in time, Suprem...
没有时间了
There is no more time.
哈拉星没时间了
Hala is out of time.
需要帮忙吗
Need a hand?
嗯
Yeah.
把那激光拿给我 三微米
Will you hand me that laser? Three micrometres.
哇
Wow.
你走过女巫咒圈就能这样
So you can do that because you walked through a witch hex?
对
Yep.
弹指事件后 他们不再派我们上太空
When I got blipped back, they weren't sending us to space anymore.
只能调查地球异常现象
Grounded us to investigate earthbound anomalies.
那一定不好受
That must have been hard.
你妈说你的梦想是上太空
Your mom told me that you always dreamed of going to space.
你想证明自己
That you had something to prove.
你说你一转眼就回来了
You said you'd be back before I knew it.
什么
What?
当你离开时
When you left...
你说你一转眼就回来了
you said you'd be back before I knew it.
我是认真的 但我不知道
I meant what I said. I just, I didn't know...
自己会陷入什么处境
what I was getting myself into.
我不知道怎么对一个小女生解释
I didn't know how to explain to a little girl that...
认真看待你每句话的小女生
A little girl that hung on your every word.
如果你知道
If you knew...
我原本会回来
I was going to come back.
只是...
I just...
有些人需要我
There was people that needed me.
我们也需要你 卡萝
We needed you, Carol.
嘿
Hey.
希望你不介意 我没别的衣服
I hope you don't mind. I didn't have any other clothes.
没关系
It's totally fine.
你穿很好看
Looks good on you.
我...
I...
很抱歉
I'm really sorry...
我那样跟你说话
for the way I spoke to you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道这情况不太理想
I know that this situation isn't ideal...
但其实这样感觉很好
but it is actually nice...
船上又有了人气
having people on board again.
在这里挺寂寞的
It gets pretty lonely out here.
如果你要有人陪 我会放下一切
Anytime you need company, I will be there. I will drop everything. I will...
我愿意休学
I will drop high school.
不准
Don't do that.
可以重新开始吗
But can we start again?
你好 我是卡萝·丹佛斯
Hi, I'm Carol Danvers.
我是卡玛拉·克汗
I am Kamala Khan.
可是在泽西市街头打击犯罪时
But when I'm fighting crime on the streets of Jersey City...
我叫惊奇少女 希望没侵犯著作权
I go by Ms. Marvel, and I hope that's okay, like, copyright-wise.
我打死都没想过会见到你
Because, honestly, I never thought I'd ever get to meet you.
结果就这样 我们有了肢体接触
But now that it's happening and we're, like, touching each other...
我发现我应该先征求同意
I've realized I should have asked permission.
同名姐妹
So, twinsies.
好吧
Okay. All right.
接下来要这么办
Here's what we're gonna do.
-惊奇队长 -别再这样叫我
-Captain Marvel. -You need to stop calling me that.
-我帮你换过尿布 -才一次
-I used to change your diapers. -Oh, that was once.
听说你吐得到处都是
And then I was told you proceeded to vomit everywhere.
首先...
First of all...
这是我的船 由我来拟订计划
it's my ship, so I make the game plan.
抱歉 你最近领导过团队吗
Oh, I'm sorry. When's the last time you led a team?
上星期就有
As early as last week.
呆头鹅不算
Goose doesn't count.
你指挥呆头鹅试试看
Please. You try giving Goose orders.
我们变一个团队了
Oh, my God, we're a team?
-我们不是团队 -并不是
-We're not... We're not a team. -No, no, no, we're not a team.
我 泽西市的卡玛拉·克汗
I, Kamala Khan of Jersey City...
加入惊奇队长和莫妮卡·蓝博上尉团队
am on a team with Captain Marvel and Captain Monica Rambeau...
从现在起就叫作...
who from this point onwards will now be known as...
惊奇教授
Professor Marvel.
-惊奇教授 -不行
-Professor Marvel. -No.
-不行 不过谢了 -惊奇天团
-No, no, she, she will not. But thank you. -The Marvels.
现在团名搞定了 我一直想告诉你们
Now that we've got that out of the way, team, I've been trying to tell you...
我知道她如何创造奇怪的跳跃点
I think I know how she's making the weird jump points.
她有这个
She has one of these.
我外婆的手镯
It's my nani's bangle.
达本开启第一个跳跃点时
It started glowing really weirdly...
它突然开始发光 还有...
when Dar-Benn opened that first jump point. Also...
它曾经让我穿越时空
it once traveled me through space and time...
那应该也有关系
so that's probably related.
你说的是量子手环
What you're describing is a Quantum Band.
我知道这手镯有两个
I mean, I knew there were two of these.
却没想到另一个在太空中
I just did not expect the other one to be in space.
它们是一对 你怎么有量子手环
They're a pair? How do you have a Quantum Band?
量子手环是什么
Okay. What is a Quantum Band?
神话之物 我以为是神话
A myth. Or I thought it was a myth.
是一种古文物
It's an ancient artifact.
这就是达本在MB-418上找到的
So this is what Dar-Benn found on MB-418.
然后她和卡玛拉刚好碰上
And then her and Kamala just happened to stumble into each other?
这概率也太低了吧
I mean, what are the chances?
"你所寻的 也在寻你"
"What you seek is seeking you."
就刻在手镯上
It's inscribed on the bangle.
如果克里人的传说是真的
If the Kree legends are true...
量子手环就是用来
the Quantum Bands were used to
创造宇宙中的每个跳跃点
create every jump point in the universe.
瞬间移动网络
Teleportation network.
两个量子手环合作能连结银河系
Two Quantum Bands working in unison to connect the galaxy.
这说明了我们交换缠结的状况
So that would explain our switch-y entanglement situation.
对 但达本只有一个
Yeah, yeah, but Dar-Benn only has one.
她一定在上面过载了太空锤的能量
She must be overloading it with the energy from her space hammer thingy.
它叫万能武器
It's called the Universal Weapon.
是吗 我本来想叫它宇宙杖
Oh, really? I was gonna call it Cosmi-Rod.
反正她利用它强迫不稳的跳跃点加入
Either way, she's using it to force unstable jump points into the grid.
我们得在她再创造跳跃点前找到她
We have got to get to her before she makes another one.
她船上的屏幕有星图
She had star charts and maps on the screens on her ship.
好 前往哪里
Okay. To where?
-前往恒星 -好
-To the stars? -Okay.
没关系 我有计划
It's fine. Got a plan.
我们用这个
We will use this.
-那是...? -史克鲁尔人的刑具
-Is that...? -A Skrull torture device.
等等 要戴在头上
And, wait, we put it on our heads?
对 别怕 用它来进入记忆
Yes, it's fine. You use it to access memories.
我都用它来...
I've been using it...
恢复被克里人夺走的记忆
to regain the memories that the Kree took from me.
还在用
Still?
对
Yeah.
但还有不少其他用途
But, you know, it has a lot of other uses.
很安全
It's safe.
找个自己舒服的姿势
You might wanna get comfortable.
感觉好奇怪
This is weird.
等等 回去
Wait. Go back.
她的手环吸收你的能量
Her band absorbs your energy
再改变它的方向
and redirects it.
好像你给她力量 让她对付你
It's like you gave her power to use against you.
卡玛拉
Kamala?
这个呢
What about this?
那边那些座标 看得到吗
There! Those coordinates. Can you read that?
可以 麦哲伦星系
Yes. The Magellanic Galaxy.
好 让你坐机长的位子
All right, the pilot seat's all you.
那是你吗 莫妮卡 超可爱的
Is that you, Monica? You're so cute!
不 等等
No, wait.
卡萝 你在干嘛
Carol, what are you doing?
为什么要我来 玛丽亚
Why'd you ask me to come, Maria?
妈
Mom.
癌症复发了
The cancer's back.
我要你照顾呆头鹅
So I need you to take care of Goose.
-不行 -什么意思
-No. -What do you mean "no?"
你抗癌过 会再成功的
No, I mean, you beat it once. You'll beat it again.
卡萝
Carol...
-我不会抱猫回去 -它不是猫
-I'm not taking the cat. -It's not a cat.
那天应该是你才对
It should've been you that day.
那场跑到飞机棚的蠢比赛
That stupid race to the hangar.
我根本不想当惊奇队长
I never wanted to be Captain Marvel.
蓝博上尉很适合我
Captain Rambeau suits me just fine.
到莫妮卡回来就好
And it's just until Monica gets back.
她化成灰了
She blipped.
卡萝 我不想重来一次
Carol, I don't wanna relive this.
对不起
I'm sorry.
拜托停止 卡萝
Stop now, please, Carol!
记住你为何挺身而出
Remember why you're out there.
-我找一个病人 104房 -我不清楚
-I'm looking for a patient in room 104. -I don't know. I don't know what to tell you.
记得回家
And remember to come home.
你妈去世了
Your mom, she died, honey.
不 不 不
No. No, no, no!
千万别再那样
Never do that again.
抱歉 我不是故意的
I'm sorry. It wasn't on purpose.
所以你妈...
Wait, so your mom...
在我化成灰烬后过世了
Passed away while I was blipped.
等我回来
And when I came back...
已经没人在了
no one was there.
好了
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
她应该很棒 真遗憾
She seemed really cool. I'm sorry.
她是啊
She was.
她是最棒的
She was the best.
我们只能靠现有的资讯
Well, we have to make do with what we know right now.
这是我们知道的
Here is what we do know.
寰宇神经瞬移网络
The Universal Neural Teleportation Network...
是时空连续体中的虫洞系统
is a system of wormholes through the space-time continuum
亦即跳跃点
aka, jump points...
让我们能在不同行星系之间跳跃
which allows us to hop between different planetary systems.
它能延伸与重新配置太空
Basically, it stretches and reconfigures space
又不破坏时空
without rupturing the continuum.
就像水力压裂 钻越多孔
Like fracking, the more holes you drill...
页岩就越不稳 然后发生地震
the more destabilized the shale becomes and then... earthquake.
总之 如果她继续创造跳跃点
Bottom line, if she keeps creating these jump points...
情况就会迅速恶化
it's gonna get really bad, really fast.
问题是 她想要什么
Question is, what does she want?
塔奈星过去遭克里人占领
Tarnax used to be occupied by the Kree, so...
也许这次攻击是警告
maybe the attack was a warning?
她可能攻击另一个前移居地吗
So, she could be after another former colony?
麦哲伦星系有前克里人移居地吗
Is there a former Kree colony in the Magellanic?
克里人曾经遍及四分之一的银河系
At one point the Kree colonized 25% of the galaxy, so...
如果她只想摧毁塔奈星
If all she wanted was to destroy Tarnax...
为何不发动军队或用炸弹
why not bring in an army or use a bomb or something?
为何用跳跃点
Why a jump point?
对 跳跃点不是武器 而是运输工具
You're right. Jump points aren't weapons, they're means of transportation.
每个跳跃点都有两面
Every jump point has two sides...
如果塔奈星的大气被吸走
so if Tarnax's atmosphere was siphoned away...
-一定会去某个地方 -哈拉星
-it had to go somewhere, or... -Hala.
克里内战
The Kree Civil War...
造成哈拉星的天然资源枯竭
basically bankrupted Hala of its natural resources.
空气几乎不适合呼吸
The air is barely breathable...
-他们饱受干旱之苦 -干旱?
-they're suffering from a drought. -A drought?
那她接下来可能要找水
So, she could be after water next.
好 麦哲伦星系哪里有
Okay. Where in the Magellanic can we find...
阿拉丹拿星
Aladna.
表面99.63%是海洋
Oceans cover 99.63% of the planet.
好精确的数字 你去过
That is a very specific stat. You've been there.
对
Yeah.
她口气怪怪的
She said that really weird.
-你怎么怪怪的 -好
-Yeah. Why are you being weird? -Okay.
我们同意去阿拉丹拿星
Consensus on Aladna.
-是 -我们就去吧
-Aye. -Yeah, I say we do it.
去阿拉丹拿星 抢走达本的手镯
Get to Aladna and separate Dar-Benn from that bangle.
目的地有了
We have our heading.
卡玛拉 你不准参加太空冒险
Kamala, you are not going on any space adventures.
尼克告诉我它们有多危险
Nicholas has told me how dangerous they can be.
叫他福瑞啦 天啊
It's just "Fury." God.
你们在哪 爸呢
Wait. Where are you guys? Where is Abu?
在地狱 这个人带我们到地狱
Hell. This man has taken us to Hell.
地狱 所以我是魔鬼啰
Hell? So that means I'm the devil?
-真的吗 福瑞 -他们坚持
-Really, Fury? -They insisted,
而且你爸不太适应太空旅行
and your dad is not adjusting very well to space travel.
宝贝 我搭疯狂太空电梯往上升
Hey, babe, so I'm in this crazy space elevator and we're going up.
或者往下坠
Or maybe we're going down.
-太空里有方向吗 -有
-Are there directions in space? -Yes, there are.
不准拍摄
But no filming.
好
Oh. Okay.
帮帮我
Help me.
福瑞 情况还好吗
Fury, everything okay?
又碰到一个突波
We've had another surge.
整个网络上都有通报
Reports are coming in across the network.
好像大家都受到影响
It seems everyone's been affected.
我们得阻止她再创造跳跃点
Well, we need to stop her from making another one...
同时也不能冒险在银河中交换位置
and we can't risk intergalactic body swapping in the meantime.
克汗太太 你女儿必须留在我船上
Mrs. Khan, I'm sorry, but your daughter will have to stay aboard my ship...
-直到我们查出原因 -不行
-until we can get to the bottom of this. -Oh, no, no, no.
赞啦
Yes!
你们要放她走
You will let her go.
克汗太太 没那么简单
Mrs. Khan, it is not that simple.
我们需要卡玛拉
We need Kamala.
妈 我们发现外婆的另一只手镯
Ammi, we found Nani's other bangle...
有个奇怪又吓人的美女
and there's this weirdly beautiful but kind of terrifying woman...
用它来伤人 我们得阻止她
using the other one to hurt people. And we have to stop her.
你是说有另一只手镯
You're telling me there's another bangle.
他们会用那手镯伤害你
And they're going to use that bangle to hurt you?
莫妮卡会照顾她
Monica will take care of her.
我们会的 也会确保她平安回家
We will. And we will make sure she gets back home in one piece.
我保证
I promise.
继续进行
Stay the course.
我们想办法关闭那些跳跃点
We'll figure out how to close those jump points.
卡玛拉 听我说
Kamala, you listen to me.
如果你出事
If anything happens to you...
我会杀了她
I will kill her.
你跟她说
You tell her that.
我爱你 宝贝
I love you, beta.
我更爱你
I love you more.
-她说什么 -没有
-Wait, what did she just say? -Nothing.
没人比惊奇队长更在乎
Nobody cares more than Captain Marvel...
没人比她吃更多苦头
and nobody gets more grief for it.
相信我 卡萝会好好照顾卡玛拉
Trust me. Kamala is in good hands with Carol.
那只猫有什么毛病
What's wrong with that cat?
它非常怪
It's acting very weird.
而且看起来有点胖
Also, Mr. Fury, she's looking little pudgy.
你喂它吃太多了
I think you're overfeeding her.
呆头鹅
Goose.
Goose!
萤火虫 夜灯
Firefly? Night Light.
惊奇女伯爵 惊奇夫人
Countess Marvel. Mistress Marvel?
-惊奇博士 -太夸张了
-Doctor Marvel? -That's too much.
光明博士
Doctor Bright.
惊奇教授
Professor Marvel.
新星 超新星女
Nova, Supernova Girl...
-光谱幻视 -太离谱了
-Spectrum, Spectrum-Vision. -You're doing too much.
幻视 等等 抱歉
Vision! Oh, wait. No. Sorry.
我得说几次 我不要
How many times do I have to tell you guys I do not want...
-也不需要代号 -好啦
-or need a code name? -Why?
如果我们没协调好 这都不重要
Besides, none of it matters if we're not coordinated out there.
想搞懂位置交换吗
Wanna figure out the switching thing?
交换后超能力依然有效 很好
Powers stay activated after a switch. Good to know.
好 数到三一起
Okay, everyone together on three.
准备 一 二 三 开始
Ready? One, two, three, go.
数到三干嘛还说开始
Now, why would you say "go" if we're going on three?
我知道
I'm aware.
进来
Now.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
她使眼色
She gave me eyes.
进来 进来
Now. Now.
可以等一下吗
Can you hold on for one second?
走 交换
Walk. And switch!
交换
Switch!
我会了
Hey, I got this!
对
Yes!
交换
And switch!
所以你要投资指数型基金 而非个股
That's why you wanna invest in index funds rather than in individual stocks.
当然 退休账户对节税也很重要
Of course, both a Roth IRA and 401k are important for tax purposes.
我根本没想过要做退休规划
You know, I never even thought about planning for retirement.
永远不嫌晚
Hey, it's never too late.
像我说的 也永远不嫌早
And it's never too early, like I say.
-你几岁 -306岁
-How old are you? -306.
你们同龄
Wow. Same age.
那是什么
What was that?
-我去看看 -麻烦了
-I'm gonna find out. -Please.
K区出现外来物体
Foreign object in sector K.
-我的妈呀 -别碰
-Sweet Svartalfheim. -Don't touch it.
这是什么
What is it?
我根本不知道
I haven't the foggiest idea.
-它怎么进去的 -我不知道
-How did it get in there? -I don't know.
该告诉福瑞吗
Should we tell Fury?
20秒后至跳跃点
Twenty seconds to the jump point.
你们知道这有多夸张吗
Do you guys realize how crazy this is right now?
我跟两个超级英雄在太空船上
Like, I'm in a spaceship with two superheroes.
现在上厕所来不及了吗
Also, is it too late to go to the bathroom?
我快憋不住了
Because I feel like it's gonna hit really soon.
没人会相信我 就像...
No one would believe me. Like my...
娜琪亚 她绝不会...
Nakia, she would never...
(阿拉丹拿星 麦哲伦星系)
好 来吧 通讯器
Okay. Here we go. Comms.
哇
Wow!
-我一直想要这个 -谢谢
-I've always wanted one of these. -Thank you.
-测试 一二三 -卡玛拉
-Testing. Testing, one, two, three. -Kamala. Kamala.
我们听到了 谢谢
We hear you, baby. Thank you.
出发之前很快讲一下
So, real quick before we get sucked in...
这什么
What the hell is that?
我得提醒你们 我在这里很有名
I should warn you that I'm kind of famous here.
你知道你在哪都很红吧
Well, you do know you're famous everywhere, right?
这里不一样 我帮王子解决法律问题
This one's kinda different. I helped the prince with a legal issue.
了解
Okay.
嗯 走吧
Mm-hmm. Let's go.
无论如何
No matter what...
遵照我的指示
follow my lead.
阿拉丹拿文化很特殊
Aladnean culture is very specific.
所以我们得参与一项仪式
So, there's gonna be a bit of a ceremony we have to do...
总之保持镇定
but just... stay cool.
美丽的阿拉丹拿
Fair Aladna...
它是和平的交叉路口
it's a peaceful crossroads
本象限之钻
Diamond of the quadrant...
阿拉丹拿 我们的家园
Aladna, our home
小朋友 请问
Hi, small child, could you tell...
美丽的阿拉丹拿
Fair Aladna...
时间彷佛停止
as if no time has passed
真高兴你回家了
So excited that you're home
我们的王妃回家了
Our princess is home
王妃
Princess?
只是个小细节
It's a technicality.
卡萝 怎么回事
Carol. What is happening?
他们的语言是歌曲
Their language is Song.
除非用唱的 否则他们听不懂
Most of them won't understand you unless you sing. Come on.
前往盛宴 阳王子设宴
Going to the banquet Prince Yan's at the banquet
嗨 嗨 你好
Hi. Oh, hi, hello.
前往盛宴 前往盛宴
Going to the banquet Going to the banquet
王子在哪里 王子在哪里 嘿
Where's the prince? Where's the prince? Hey, hey, hey
前往 前往盛宴
Going, going, going, going Going to the banquet
你们怎么不跳
Why aren't you guys dancing?
我在跳了
I am dancing.
跳舞是生命
Dancing is life
快到了
Oh, we're almost there.
好漂亮 嗨 好
How angelic. Hi... Okay. All right.
哇
Wow.
他们嗑了什么 给我来一点
Oh, my gosh, give me some of what they're having.
-你们要是告诉别人 -什么
-If you tell anyone about... -What?
说你是妖娇美丽的王妃
That you're a pretty, pretty princess?
原来这就是你说的"法律问题"
So, that's what you meant when you said "legal issue."
这是各取所需的婚姻 就像外交措施
It is a marriage of convenience. It's more of a diplomatic act, you know?
母系社会的权力斗争
It's like, there was a power struggle. Matriarchal society.
我们是朋友 说来话长
We are friends. It's a long story.
也许你能唱出来
Maybe you could sing it.
才不要
Maybe not.
我们到了
We're here.
靠
Damn.
-你看见他们抵达 -你好
-You saw them arrive -Oh, hello
我知道你为何爱来这里了
Well, okay, I see why you like to come here.
-注意 -是
-Attention -Yes
很高兴向在场所有人宣布
A pleasure to announce To this lovely roomful
两张新面孔
Two new faces
一张可以再开心点
One could be more cheerful
哈 哈 哈
Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha
但是 我们摇摇铃
But nonetheless, we ring the bells
欢迎哪位来说明
To usher in, who, pray tell?
那就是
None other than
一 二 三
One, two, three
惊奇天团
The Marvels!
-惊奇天团 -惊奇天团
-The Marvels -The Marvels?
赞
Yes!
怎么已经定名了
How is that even a thing already?
-好 镇定一点 -王子呢
-Okay, let's be cool. -Where's the prince?
我...
That's...
怎么搞的
What the hell?
-她在干嘛 -入境随俗
-What is she doing? -She's respecting the flow.
这一次
How long
能与舞伴共度多久
do I have with my dance partner this time?
阳
Yan...
-我们都有... -怎么回事
-we are all... -What is happening?
-危险 -什么
-in danger -What?
-队长需要我们帮助 -帮助
-The Captain needs our help -Help!
达本来了
Dar-Benn is coming
我现在心情好复杂
I'm feeling so many feelings right now.
阿拉丹拿不怕她
Oh, Aladna's not afraid of her
邀她下来 让她踏上土地
Invite her down put her feet on the ground
给我一个机会
Give me a chance here...
-以免不可收拾 -引狼入室
-before it gets too messy -So lead the wolf inside our walls
相信靠你一个人
And trust that you alone...
-就能阻止大军 -我可曾让你失望
-can stop an army? -Have I ever let you down?
你的粉丝小说能写几章
How many chapters of your Captain Marvel fan fiction is this giving you?
-好多章 -别忘记
-So many. -and don't forget...
别忘记
Don't forget
我不孤单
I'm not alone
莫妮卡
Monica.
我来自星星的王妃
My Princess from the star...
抱歉 停 我们需要谈谈
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Stop. Please stop. We need to talk.
-好 我们来谈 -好
-Okay, let's talk. -Okay.
等等 他不必唱歌吗
Oh, wait. He doesn't have to sing?
对 他会双语
Yeah, he's bilingual.
我们穿着非常不得体
We are severely underdressed.
能帮我们找战斗服吗
But could you get us something a little more battle-ready?
当然
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
目前的推论
Theories so far?
最佳状况是一次性的害虫问题
At best, a one-off pest problem.
最糟的可能是敌人放置的
At worst, an enemy plant.
某种感染性生物武器
Some kinda infestation bioweapon.
也可能是内贼所为
Or it could be from a traitor from within.
先别往那边想 你说的这个卵
Well, let's not go there yet. This... egg you say...
继续研究 如果发现什么
let's just continue to study it, and if anything...
警告 侦测到29个新物体
Warning. Twenty-nine new objects detected.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
(发现个数  30)
光女士怎么样
What about Lady of Light?
-频率 脉冲星 -不要 不要
-Frequency. Pulsar. -No. No.
脉冲星光女士
Pulsar Light Lady.
绝对不行 这服装太扯了
Absolutely not. These... These are too much, right?
-当然 -哪会
-Definitely. -No.
速战速决 别太浮夸
We make this quick. Nothing grandiose.
三位必须消失 但别跑远
You three need to disappear. But stay close.
我的强项
My specialty.
会成功的 阳
This will work, Yan.
记住 尽量别无意中交换位置
Remember, we wanna keep unintentional switching to a minimum.
尽量拖住她
Entertain her as long as you possibly can.
莫妮卡和我会突袭她
Monica and I will get the jump on her.
我们会抢到手镯
And we'll get the bangle.
时间到了
It's time.
至高者 你怎么来了
Supremor, why have you come?
我来赦免你反抗克里帝国的罪
I've come here to pardon you for your crimes against the Kree Empire.
跪下
Kneel.
向你跪?
To you?
-我绝对不跪 -好
-I will never kneel. -Okay.
可恶
Damn it!
用你的围巾
Use your scarf.
快去
Go!
找到她了
I found her.
莫妮卡 你在哪里
Monica, where are you?
莫妮卡 跟我交换
Monica, tag me in.
一 二
One, two...
别这么做
Don't do this.
你来不及了
You're too late.
你在哪里拿到的
Where did you get that?
我外婆 她寄给我的
My grandma, she sent it to me in the mail.
-给我 -卡玛拉 快跑
-Give it to me. -Kamala, run.
上船
Get to the ship.
有了它 你的力量只会使我更强大
With this, your powers only make me stronger.
突波破坏了我们的系统
The surges are frying our systems.
我们要处理这些吗
Are we doing something about these?
太空电梯断线了
The space elevator's offline.
你都没有好消息吗
You ever come in here with good news?
半数逃生舱故障了
Half the evacuation pods just went down.
这不是好消息
That's not good news.
你们上船了吗
Are you guys in?
上了
In.
全体战斗机改向
Redirect all fighters.
解除自动驾驶
Disengaging autopilot.
天啊 起飞
Oh, my God. Okay, here we go. Here we go.
莫妮卡
Monica?
莫妮卡 往下坠了 莫妮卡
Monica, we're going down, Monica!
我以为你会开
I thought you could drive this thing!
卡萝 快下来
Carol! Get down here.
别急
Hold that thought.
这小姐太扯了
Can you believe this woman?
队长 我的队长
O, Captain! My Captain!
-不 -走开
-No, no, no! -Move over.
我来启动跳跃点
I'm activating a jump point.
-不 我能甩掉她 -另外20艘呢
-No, I can lose her. -And what about the other 20 ships?
我有办法
I can do this.
-导弹锁定 -姐姐
-Missile lock. -Guys?
导弹锁定
Missile lock.
导弹来袭
Incoming missiles.
-击中倒数 五 -该离开了
-Impact in five... -We need to leave now.
-我不能让旧事重演 -四
-I can't let this happen again. -four...
-已经重演了 -三 二
-It already has. -three, two...
-我做得到 -你会害死我们
-I can do this. -And you'll kill us trying.
跳跃点启动
Jump point activated.
我们丢下阿拉丹拿星自生自灭
We left Aladna to fend for themselves.
达本要抢我的手镯
Dar-Benn was gonna get my bangle.
我做出困难决定 跟你在塔奈星一样
So I made a tough call like you did on Tarnax.
别学我 我整个搞砸了
Don't try to be like me. I messed this whole thing up.
如果我们没缠结在一起
If we weren't entangled...
如果我们不在这里 你就能击败达本
if we weren't here, then you could have beat Dar-Benn.
对不起
And I'm sorry.
不 你不懂
No, you don't understand.
克里人已被人工智能统治一千年
The Kree had been ruled by an AI for a millennia...
造成他们陷入战争
that led them into a war.
我以为要阻止它 只有摧毁它
And I thought the only way to stop it was to destroy it.
可是我却...
But I just...
越帮越忙
made it worse.
我是他们内战开打的原因
I'm the reason why the civil war started in the first place...
我害他们无法呼吸空气
I'm the reason why they couldn't breathe the air.
所以我才得到歼灭者的称号
That's how I got the name Annihilator.
我不要你们看到我的那一面
And I never wanted you to see that version of me.
所以你才没回来过
Is that why you never came back?
我想如果将功赎罪
I thought if I fixed it...
我就能回家
then I could come home.
卡萝
Carol.
家人不是那样子
That's not how family works.
我根本不期望你当无敌的惊奇队长
I never expected you to be the mighty Captain Marvel.
我只要你
I just wanted you.
我的阿姨
My aunt.
好高兴你在这里
I'm really glad that you're here now.
还有你
And you, too.
我很高兴能在这里
I'm glad to be here.
希望看得出来 我也很抱歉
I hope that goes without saying. And I am sorry...
刚开始热情过头
for coming on too strong at the beginning.
我没给你太多空间做自己
I did not give you a lot of space to be a real person.
我们得找到她
We have to find her.
她可能在任何地方
I mean, but she could be anywhere.
不 不是任何地方
No, not anywhere.
她会锁定我关心的人
She's targeting the people that I care about...
抢走我每个家园的资源
and stealing resources from every place I call home.
我们必须警告福瑞
We have to warn Fury.
这是紧急状况
This is an emergency.
神刃太空站全员立刻至逃生舱报到
All S.A.B.E.R. personnel must report to an evacuation pod immediately. Walk.
-别跑 -只有一个逃生站正常运作
-Do not run. -We only have one evacuation bay online.
所以15艘逃生舱
Which means that all we have left...
却得撤离350人
to evacuate 350 personnel are 15 escape pods...
每艘硬挤能载10人 根本不够
which seat five, 10, if we squeeze. It's nowhere near enough.
剩下的逃生舱尽量塞人
Well, fill the remaining ones with as many people as you can...
-再想备案 -这是紧急状况...
-then come up with a Plan B. -This is an emergency. All S.A.B.E.R...
不 等等
No, no, no.
阿米尔 去帮他们
Aamir. Go help them.
好
Okay, okay. Okay.
让我来
I got this.
我的客厅
My living room.
呆头鹅
Goose?
呆头鹅 你怎么...
Goose, how'd you...
过来 快点
Come here. Come. Come on.
对 过来 看看你
Yes. Yes. Come here. Look at you.
你看
Look!
别弄我的眼睛
Oh, no, not my good eye!
我们只剩一艘逃生舱
We only have one escape pod left.
完蛋了
We're doomed.
到最后...
In the end...
我们都不能选择如何从这一世
none of us choose how we transition from this life...
转移到下一世
to the next.
什么 不
What? No!
叫所有人到逃生站
Get everyone to the evacuation deck.
快去
Now!
这是在干嘛
What are we doing?
-我没办法 你能吗 -我来
-I can't. Can you? -I got it.
怎么了 亲爱的家人
What is going on, fam?
卡玛拉
Kamala?
卡玛拉 优素福 是卡玛拉
Kamala! Yusuf, Kamala!
卡玛拉
Kamala! Kamala!
你平安回来了 宝贝
You're back safely, beta.
-嗨 -你没死
You're not dead.
我跟地球失联
I've lost contact with Earth.
我们正式进入弃船阶段
We're officially at abandon-ship phase.
吐出来
Spit him out.
-吐出来 -不
-Spit him out. -No, no, no.
不 这是我的计划
No. That's the plan.
这是计划?
That's the plan?
运送一个猫咪家族比几百人简单
to transport a family of cats than hundreds of crew members.
我们真的要移猫
So, we're literally herding cats?
过来 猫咪
Come here, kitty.
神刃太空站人员注意
Attention, S.A.B.E.R. crew.
别跑 让佛莱肯吃掉你
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
你不会有事的
You will be fine.
神刃太空站人员
S.A.B.E.R. crew.
别跑 让佛莱肯吃掉你
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
别跑
Stop running.
对不起
I'm sorry.
别跑 让佛莱肯吃掉你
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
别跑
Stop running.
(侦测到输入)
(星图)
我找到她了
Guys, I found her.
-快点 快走 -来
-Come on. Come on, move. -Hey! Come on.
过来
Come on, come here.
-快去 -快
-Go, go, go. -Come on, come on.
-到太空船站 -好 快点
-Go to the spacecraft bay. -Okay. Come on.
优素福 别用腰带
Come on. Yusuf, stop with your belt.
不要 谢谢
Nope. No. No, no, no. Thank you. No.
过来
Come, come, come.
放心 小猫 去找卡玛拉
Don't you worry, little one. Here, go to Kamala. Go to Kamala.
-过来 -我发现达本了
-There you go, come, come. -I found Dar-Benn.
什么
What?
她要我们的太阳
She wants our sun.
你又要离开了
You leavin' again?
对
Yeah.
宇宙还是不安全
Ammi, the universe isn't safe.
如果宇宙不安全 你们就不安全
And if the universe isn't safe, that means you guys aren't safe.
如果你们不...
And if you guys aren't...
听我说
Listen to me.
你肩负着更重大的使命
You are chosen for a greater purpose, okay?
你当然该走了
So, of course you must go now.
但我永远不会放开你
But I will never let you go.
你懂吧
You understand that, right?
平安归来 女儿
Come back safely, beta.
最好回来 我不想当独生子
You better. I don't wanna be an only child.
不要又自己应付这两个
Not again. Not with these two.
带着手镯去找那坏蛋好吗
You think it's wise taking that bangle to the bad guy?
福瑞先生说得对 给我 我带回家
Yes. Mr. Fury's right. Give it to me. I will take it home.
达本开启了另一个跳跃点
Dar-Benn's opened another jump point...
需要两只手镯才能关闭它
and we're gonna need both bangles to close it.
那你最好别让她抢走
Then I guess you'd better make damn sure she doesn't get her hands on it.
了解
Understood.
天啊 福瑞先生
Oh, God, Mr. Fury...
-你飞错方向了 -克汗太太 我知道
-you are going in the wrong direction! -Mrs. Khan, I know!
-成功了 福瑞先生 -我什么都没做
-You did it, Mr. Fury! -I didn't do anything.
你在祷告吗
Are you praying?
别停 我们需要众神帮忙
Don't stop! We need all the help we can get!
阿门
Amen!
我的妈呀
Holy cow!
福瑞先生
Mr. Fury!
她来了
There she is...
歼灭者本尊
the Annihilator herself.
结束了 达本
It's over, Dar-Benn.
还没
No, not yet.
我知道你会不顾一切保护哈拉星
I know that you would do anything to protect Hala.
这将是克里人的末日 一切的末日
This will be the end of the Kree. It will be the end of everything.
你夺走我的一切 我只是以牙还牙
You took from me. I'm simply repaying the favor.
来 手环交给我
Now, give me the band.
你忘了一样东西
You're forgetting something.
-什么 -我
-What? -Me.
本来可以很轻松解决的
This could have been so much easier.
不好说 我们的胜率比较高
I don't know. I like our odds.
你又恢复恶名了
You're living up to your name again.
我也不想这样
I didn't want this.
死亡似乎紧跟着你
Death seems to follow you.
其实不必落得这种下场 达本
It doesn't have to end like this, Dar-Benn.
拜托把手镯给我们
Please, just give us the bangle.
做梦
I won't!
哈拉星的太阳因你而亡
Hala's sun died because of you.
你凭什么不必付出代价
Why shouldn't you repay us?
也许她应该
Maybe she should.
你们太阳核心的反应减缓了
The reaction in your sun's core has slowed.
它需要极大能量才能重启
It needs an incredible amount of energy to jump-start it...
你有办法 卡萝
and that's what you have, Carol.
你能用你的力量拯救哈拉星
You can use your powers to save Hala.
但我没做过那种事
But I've never done anything like that before.
这几天我做了许多没做过的事
In the last couple of days I have done a lot of things I have never done before.
你可以的
You got this.
为了哈拉星
For Hala.
敢轻举妄动 我马上杀了她
Try anything and I'll kill her faster than you can move.
卡萝
Carol!
不
No!
你会没办法存活
You won't survive this.
达本 听我说
Dar-Benn, listen to me.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
我没交换位置
I didn't switch.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
我好高兴你没事
I'm so glad you're okay.
你抢到手镯了
You got the bangles.
我们会用得上
We are gonna need those.
起来吧 王妃
Okay, come on, Princess.
我们在看什么
So, what are we looking at?
一个自我传播奇异点 具有负质量
A self-propagating singularity with negative mass...
与非典型物理特性
and non-Newtonian topology.
她在时空中扯开一个洞
She tore a hole in space-time.
那是个不同的现实 逐渐扩张过来
That is a different reality bleeding into ours.
我们能解决吗
Can we even fix that?
理论上 你和卡萝能复制
In theory, you and Carol can reproduce the same amount of energy...
用来打开它的能量
that was used to open it.
我吸收再释放它 但从洞里进行
I will absorb it and then release it, but from inside the tear.
但交换位置怎么了
But what about the switching?
我们的超能力不再缠结了
Our powers aren't entangled anymore.
我想那是好事
Well, that's a good thing, I guess.
等等 你要我们用在时空结构中
But, wait. You want us to blast you with the same amount of power...
砸出一个洞的能量轰击你
that punched a hole in the fabric of space-time?
如果要把它补起来 没错
If we wanna un-punch it, yeah.
莫妮卡
Monica...
你会需要这个
You're gonna need this.
感觉如何 惊奇少女
How are you feeling, Ms. Marvel?
这些手镯穿越了时空
These bangles traveled through space and time.
找到我
To find me.
我天生就该做这件事
I was born for this.
必须立刻开始
It has to be now.
你妈一定会很骄傲
Your mom would be proud.
更高 更远 更快
Higher, further, faster.
它在闭合了 莫妮卡 快离开
It's closing, Monica. You've got to get out of there.
我不能离开 卡萝
I can't leave, Carol.
什么意思
What? What do you mean?
我不能离开
I can't leave.
我得完成任务
I have to finish the job.
不 莫妮卡 它合起来了 你会困住
No! Monica, it's closing. You'll be trapped!
没关系
It's okay.
快啊
Come on.
我始终明白我得留下
Always knew I would have to stay.
卡玛拉
Kamala.
卡玛拉 你拯救了世界
Kamala, you saved the world.
你怎么哭了 你怎么哭了
Why are you crying? Why are you crying?
怎么回事
What happened?
我们失去了莫妮卡
We lost Monica.
她困在另一边
She got stuck on the other side.
卡萝呢
And Carol?
她去实现一个承诺
She went to fulfill a promise.
(哈拉星)
情况如何
How are things?
那些星球预计能完全恢复
The planets are expected to make a full recovery.
有一组科学家被派去协助哈拉星
And a team of scientists are being sent to Hala to try and help their people.
我指的不是这个
That's not what I meant.
(路易斯安那州)
(呆头鹅的零食)
这边写"厨房" 但都是辣酱包
This says "Kitchen," but there are all these hot sauce packets...
还有一个很诡异的托盘
And then there's this very bizarre-looking tray...
不过看起来质量很好
which I will say is a very good quality, though.
你可以留着
You can keep it.
-不 卡萝 -还能去哪
-Oh, no, no, Carol, I just... -Where else would they go?
我只是不懂这怎么在箱子里...
I just don't understand how it's in the box...
那是我的
Oh, yeah, yeah, it was for me.
太空之大刷新了我的三观
The vastness of it just gives you a whole new perspective on life.
就是说啊
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
而且冷到爆
And it was surprisingly cool.
这里棒呆了
This place is amazing.
没错
Yeah, it is.
你还会开那架吗
Hey, do you still fly that thing?
-想去看看吗 -想
-You wanna check it out? -I do.
好
All right.
等一下 过来
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Come here. Come here. Come here.
-我好开心你平安回家 -好啦
-I'm so happy that you're home safe, beta. -Okay.
阿米尔
Aamir...
这间房子很适合成家
this would be a lovely house to raise a family in, you know?
阿米尔
Aamir.
实在太酷了
This is so cool.
让你坐机长的位子
Pilot seat's all you.
我们起飞吧
Let's fly this thing.
其实我没钥匙
I actually don't have the key.
我只负责保管
I'm just looking after it.
直到莫妮卡回来
Just until Monica gets back?
对
Yeah.
直到莫妮卡回来
Just until Monica gets back.
我好想她
I really miss her.
我们合作无间
We were good together.
这让我想到
Which got me thinking...
披萨送来了
Pizza delivery.
好的
Okay.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
凯特·毕夏普
Kate Bishop.
你以为你是世上唯一的超级英雄吗
Did you think you're the only kid superhero in the world?
-我23岁 -我知道
-Well, I'm 23. -Oh, I know.
(神刃太空站)
我在看你的资料
I've been reading up on you.
那是哪来的
Where did you get that?
在我沙发上发现的
I found it in my couch.
好吧
Okay.
你刚成为一个更庞大宇宙的一员
You've just become part of a much larger universe.
目前主要只有我一个
Which, at the moment, is just me, mostly.
但我有征询过别人
I do have feelers out, though.
-知道蚁人有女儿吗 -你想干嘛
-Did you know Ant-Man had a daughter? -What do you want?
我要组成一个团队
I'm putting together a team.
我要你加入
And I want you on it.
拜托啦
Please?
《惊奇队长2》
妈
Mom?
"Mom"?
-妈  -"妈?"
-Mom! -"Mom?"
我好想你
I've missed you so much!
你想我?
You missed me?
-对不起 -好 好 好
-I'm so sorry. I'm... -Okay. Okay. Okay.
看着我 没关系 你没事
Hey, hey, look at me. It's okay. You're okay. Hey.
我们的神秘访客还好吗
How's our mysterious visitor?
她好像有点头脑不清
She seems a little disoriented.
这是哪里 怎么回事
Where... Where are we? What happened?
我们还希望你能告诉我们
We were hoping you could tell us.
我们只知道双星发现了你
All we know is that Binary found you.
我猜你通过时空中的裂缝
My theory? You somehow crossed through a tear in space-time.
现在你在你那个世界的平行现实里
You are now in a reality parallel to your own.
当然 那是不可能的
Which is, of course, impossible.
我想现在状况可能有点混淆
I think there might be a little confusion happening.
混淆只是踏上知识之路的第一步
Confusion is but the first step on the journey to knowledge.
好 由我来接手
Okay. I'll take it from here.
查尔斯要求报告最新状况
Charles asked for an update.
我晚点再过来看你
I'll come by and check on you later.
你是谁
Who are you?
糟了
Oh, shit.